COLIN O'NEILL UX/UI DESIGNER

High-energy and reliable UX/UI Designer targeting a collaborative and progressive work environment after now having completed a Bachelor of Arts Degree at Simon Fraser University's School of Interactive Arts & Technology (SIAT). Skills include using various design programs for Product Design, User Experience Design, 3D Modelling and Video Production.

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University School of Interactive Arts & Technology, BA September 2018 - June 2024

<u>Skills</u>

- o UX Research/Documentation
- o User Experience Design
- o User Interface Design
- Wireframing
- o Product Design
- o Data Visualization
- Illustrating
- o Design Systems
- o Information Architecture

Tools

- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma
- Power BI
- o Proto-Pie
- Adobe XD
- Balsamiq
- HTML/CSS/Javascript/Typescript
- Miro/Figjam

Work Experience

Fraser Health Authority, (FHA)

Role: UX/UI Designer January 2024 - Present Co-op/Employee Responsible for developing design system components, dashboard wireframing in both low and high fidelity, conducting user research and documentation.

Precision NanoSystems Inc.

Role: Graphic Designer May 2021 - December 2021 Co-op Worked on various creative projects related to the company image using The Adobe Creative Suite, including social media graphics, diagram designs, and editing presentation layouts.

UX DESIGN PROJECTS

(FHA) Advanced Analytics Platform: Dashboard Pages

Role: UX/UI Designer February - June 2024

• Discussed with consultants and experts regarding the design of the new Advanced Analytics platform intended for Fraser Health staff to view data and trends to improve operations and patient outcomes.

(FHA) Advance Analytics Platform: Graph Design System

Role: UX/UI Designer February - June 2024

• Created a modular design system for CAADSI's Advance Analytics Platform prototyping, which includes a wide variety of graphs, allowing users to create the low and hi-fidelity graphs they need with a simple switch.

(FHA) iTracker: Acuity Score Page

Role: UX/UI Designer January - June 2024

• Designed the Acuity Score section on Fraser Health's iTracker platform in a user-friendly manner to enhance the experience.



corlinoneill@gmail.com
in www.linkedin.com/in/colin-m-o-neill
colinoneilldesigns.com